

BYRON RODRIGUEZ

SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING FULL STACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT



Phone

+502 3882-4965



Email

byron303@gmail.com



Address

Panajachel, Guatemala



URL

Byron Rodriguez Aragon



EDUCATION

- Full-Stack Developer
 4Geeks Academy 2023
- Meta Social Media Marketing Specialization
 Meta and Coursera 2022
- Google Digital Marketing and E-Commerce Certificate
 - Google and Coursera 2022
- Bachelor in Clinical
 Psychology
 Universidad Panamericana
 2015



LANGUAGES

- English
- Spanish



ABOUT ME

I have an educational background in clinical psychology, but digital marketing and sales have been the main focus of my professional career. Over the last two years, I have been focusing on web development and recently graduated as a full-stack developer from a programming boot camp at 4Geeks Academy.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Social Media ManagerHomes Guatemala

2016 - 2021

Social Media Manager and Marketing Coordinator: Content creator. Meta Ads. Wordpress. Video Editing. Email Marketing. SEO and Copywriting. Realtor for residential housing.

Sales SupervisorRoyal Caribbean International

2014- 2016

Representatives
Onboarding Trainer and Special Services for Royal
Caribbean

Supervisor for Customer Service Sales

Recruitment - Travel Coordinator 2010 - 2013Capgemini

Travel and recruitment coordinator for onboarding process and human resources in North America.



MY SKILLS & EXPERTISE

Digital Marketing	Sales
Meta Ads Manager	Customer Service
Video Editing	Microsoft Office
Front-End Development	Amazon Listing Optimization
Back-End Development	Amazon PPC
Email Marketing	SEO